(Leonard:)Wow. Wouldn't think there'd
(Leonard:)be that many.
Number 42!
(Leonard:)Whoa!
(Bernadette:)Isn't she a pip?
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)Proxima Centauri's
the nearest star.
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)The celestial bodies
that follow are
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)Alpha Centauri A, Toli,
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)Barnard's Star,
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)Wolf 359...
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)Lalande 21185,
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)Sirius A, Sirius B,
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)BL-Ceti, UV-Ceti,
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)Ross 154...
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)Ross 248...
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)Epsilon Eridani,
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)Lac-9352,
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)Ross 128,
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)Procyon A...
(Sheldon(rhythmically, while walking down the stairs):)Oh, darn, that's wrong!